citizensbank.ca 2016-10-30

# Privacy | Citizens Bank of Canada

Privacy and information security are at the top of the list when it comes to the concerns of Canadians.

We collect your personal information so we can provide you with a high level of service and financial products. To do this, we need to fully understand your financial needs and your situation. Sometimes that means we need more than just your name and address. 

**Privacy Statement**

Citizens Bank of Canada, its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (Collectively Citizens Bank) may collect personal information from me, from product and service arrangements I have made with or through you, from credit bureaus and other financial institutions, and from the references I have provided you.

Citizens Bank may collect, use and disclose my personal information for the following purposes:

*             To provide me with financial services  
*             To understand my financial and banking needs  
*             To develop, manage and deliver products and services to me  
*             To determine my eligibility for different products and services  
*             To ensure that I receive a high standard of service  
*             To meet regulatory requirements  
*             To manage and transfer the assets and liabilities of Citizens Bank; and  
*             To verify my identity.

Citizens Bank may provide my personal information to credit bureaus and other financial institutions and, with my consent, to other parties. Citizens Bank may share my personal information with its employees and business partners, but only as needed for the provision of products and services.

Citizens Bank may also use my personal information to introduce products and services that may be of interest to me through contacting me directly (via mail, telephone calls or e-mail only), and share it, (subject to applicable law) for marketing purposes within Citizens Bank.

**Opt-out**

At any time, I can choose to opt-out of receiving direct marketing or sharing my personal information for marketing purposes. To opt-out, please fill out the [opt-out form](https://www.citizensbank.ca/docs/CBoptout.pdf) and mail to the Privacy Office.

For more information of how Citizens Bank manages your personal information, please see our [Privacy Code](https://www.citizensbank.ca/docs/CBMemberPrivacyCode.pdf).

**Questions or concerns?**  
We are interested in your concerns about privacy and security. Drop us an [email](mailto:privacy@citizensbank.ca) or write to us:

Attention: Chief Privacy Officer  
Citizens Bank of Canada  
401 - 815 W. Hastings Street  
Vancouver, BC  
V6C 1B4  
1-888-708-8307

For your protection, do not send sensitive financial information by regular email.
